(Howard:)Short jokes? Really?
You're, like,
(Howard:)a quarter of an inch
taller than me.
(Leonard:)Yeah, and don't
you forget it.
(Howard:)I had a good time.
(Bernadette:)Me, too.
(Katee Sackhoff:)Kiss her good night.
(Katee Sackhoff:)All right, now a little tongue.
GEORGE TAKEI:
Hold on there.
(George Takei:)We've only just rekindled
the romance.
(George Takei:)Let's not sully the moment
with the exchange of saliva.
(Katee Sackhoff:)Don't listen to him.
(Katee Sackhoff:)She wants it.
(Katee Sackhoff:)Tongue.
La, la, la, la, la.
(Penny:)See?
(Katee Sackhoff:)Now make the move.
(George Takei:)Mm-mmm.
Too soon.
(Katee Sackhoff:)Trust me, she's ready.
(Howard:)Make the move.
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)No, no, no.
(George Takei:)A lady wants to be wooed,
(George Takei:)courted slowly.